
const Question = [
    {
        _id: 1,
        qno:'1',
        question: 'While multiple inputs are supported visually, validation styles are only available for input groups with a single input.',
        correct_answer: '46',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, {
        _id: 2,
        qno:'2',
        question: '22222',
        correct_answer: '76',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '3',
            '2'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 3,
        qno:'3',
        question: '33333',
        correct_answer: '4777',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 4,
        qno:'4',
        question: '-444444',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 5,
        qno:'5',
        question: '-5555',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 6,
        qno:'6',
        question: '-66666',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 7,
        qno:'7',
        question: '-77777',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 8,
        qno:'8',
        question: '-88888',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 9,
        qno:'9',
       
        question: '-999',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 10,
        qno:'10',
        question: '-10000',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 11,
        qno:'11',
        question: '-svdsvds',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    },
    {
        _id: 12,
        qno:'12',
        question: '-sdvsafwfcasvca',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, {
        _id: 13,
        qno:'13',
        question: '-wefgvdvdvd',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, 
    {
        _id: 14,
        qno:'14',
        question: '-gee',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, 
    {
        _id: 15,
        qno:'15',
        question: '-wefgvdvdvd',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, 
    {
        _id: 16,
        qno:'16',
        question: '-wefgvdvdvd',
        correct_answer: '988',
        incorrect_answer: [
            '1',
            '2',
            '3'
        ]
    }, 
    


];

export default Question;